The graph  coloring here is like that we discussed in the previous video doesn't
这里的图形着色类似于我们在上一个视频中讨论的图形着色，而不是
always succeed in coloring an arbitrary graph. And it may well get stuck and not
总是能成功地给任意图形上色。它很可能会卡住而不会
be able to find a coloring. And so in that case the only conclusion we can reach is
能够找到一种颜色。所以在这种情况下我们能得出的唯一结论是
that we can't hold all the values that we'd like to register. We have more
我们不可能拥有我们想要登记的所有价值。我们还有更多
temporary values and we have registers to hold them. And those temporary values have
临时值，我们有寄存器来保存它们。这些临时值具有
to live somewhere so where should they live? Well, they're going to have to live
住在某个地方，那么他们应该住在哪里呢？嗯，他们将不得不活着
in memory. That's the only other kind of stories that we have. And so we're going
在记忆中。这是我们仅有的其他类型的故事。所以我们要去
to pick some values and spill them into memory. The ideas that we have, the
选择一些值并将它们溢出到内存中。我们拥有的想法，
picture in your mind should be. A bucket and it can hold a fixed amount of stuff.
你脑海中的画面应该是。一个水桶，它可以装固定数量的东西。
Those are the registers and when it gets too full, some of the stuff spills over
这些是收银机，当它太满时，一些东西就会溢出来。
and, and ends up some place else. Now, when does the graph coloring here do get
然后，最后去了别的地方。现在，这里的图表着色是什么时候开始的呢？
stuck? Well, this only situation which we won't be able to make progress as if all
卡住了？嗯，这是唯一一种我们不能取得进展的情况，就好像所有的
the notes have k or more neighbors. So, let's take a look at our
音符有k个或更多的邻居。那么我们来看一下我们的
favorite register interference graph when we will be using at our examples and now,
最喜欢的寄存器干扰图，当我们将在我们的示例中使用时，现在，
let's say that our, the machine we want to use only has three registers and so we,
比如说我们，我们要用的这个机器只有三个寄存器，所以我们，
instead of finding a 4-coloring of this graph, we need to find a 3-coloring. So
我们需要找的不是这个图的4-着色，而是3-着色。所以
let's think about how to find the three coloring of this graph. If we apply the
让我们考虑一下如何找到这张图的三种颜色。如果我们将
heuristic, we'll remove A from the graph but then we're going to get stuck. Because
启发式，我们会从图中去掉A，但是我们会被卡住。因为
once you take A out of the graph and it's edge is out and every node that's
一旦你把A从图中拿出来，它的边就出来了，每一个节点
left has more than has three or more neighbors as at least three neighbors. So,
Left有超过三个或更多邻居作为至少三个邻居。所以,
there's no node that we can delete from the graph and be guaranteed to be able to
我们不能从图中删除任何节点，也不能保证能够
find the coloring for it with the heuristic that we discussed in the previous video.
使用我们在上一个视频中讨论的启发式方法找到它的颜色。
So, in this situation, what we're going to do is we're going to pick and know that
因此，在这种情况下，我们要做的是选择并了解
there is a candidate for spilling. This is a know that we or a temporary that we are
有一个可能会泄漏的候选人。这是一种知道我们或暂时知道我们是
probably or we think we may have to assign into a memory location rather than to our
可能，或者我们认为我们可能必须赋值到内存位置，而不是赋值给我们的
register and let is assume for the sake of this example that we pick f and we talk
注册，为了这个示例，我们假设我们选择f并进行交谈
later about how to choose a, the know to spill, there's a number of different ways
后来关于如何选择一个，知道怎么说，有很多不同的方式
to, to chose the particular know to spill but for the illustration of this example,
为了，为了，为了这个例子的说明，选择了特定的已知信息来泄漏，
it doesn't matter how pick, we just have to pick one to remove from the. Graph. As
不管怎么挑，我们只需要挑一个就行了。图表。作为
were going to say, we're going to remove, that we going to spill F. So what we'll do
我们会说，我们要去掉，我们要把F洒出来，所以我们要做的是
then is we'll remove f from the graph just like before and then we'll continue with
然后，我们将像以前一样从图中删除f，然后我们将继续
our simplification and this will now succeed because once we move F from the
我们的简化现在会成功，因为一旦我们将F从
graph we can see that all the nodes well, actually several of the nodes have fewer
图中我们可以看到，所有的节点都很好，实际上有几个节点的数量较少
than three neighbors and so B, C, and D. Sorry, B and D both only have two
三个邻居，所以B、C和D。对不起，B和D都只有两个
neighbors when [inaudible] E and C will only have one neighbor each and so clearly
邻居当[听不见]E和C将各自只有一个邻居，并且非常清楚
coloring will now succeed and here's one order that we'll succeed with this reduced
现在上色将会成功，这里有一个订单，我们将使用此简化后的颜色成功上色
graph. After we decide to spill f and we successfully color the sub-graph, now we
图表。在我们决定溢出f并且成功地给子图着色之后，现在我们
have to try to assign a color to f and it could be, we could get lucky and discover
我得试着给f指定一种颜色，它可能是，我们可以幸运地发现
that even though f had more than there neighbors or three or more neighbors when
即使f有多于三个邻居或三个或更多邻居，当
we remove it from the graph, it could be that when we go to construct the coloring
我们将其从图中移除，这可能是因为当我们要构造着色时
for the sub-graph that. Those neighbors actually don't use all of the register. It
对于子图来说。那些邻居实际上并没有使用所有的收银机。它
could wind up being at all those neighbors, for example or assign to the
可能最终成为所有这些邻居，例如，或分配给
same register and so there are plenty of registers left over to assign to f. And
相同的寄存器，因此有大量剩余的寄存器可以分配给f和
so, this is called optimistic coloring. So we pick a candidate for spilling. We tried
所以，这叫做乐观着色。所以我们选了一个泄密的候选人。我们试过了
to color the sub-graph. Once we have a coloring for the sub-graph, now we see if
来给子图上色。一旦我们有了子图的着色，现在我们就可以看到
we just get lucky. And are able to assign a register to F. In which case we can just
我们只是走运而已。并且能够将寄存器分配给F。在这种情况下，我们可以只
go ahead and continue the color of the rest of the graph as if nothing had
继续，继续图表的睡觉颜色，就好像什么都没有
happened. So in this case let's take a look what happens. We're going add F back
发生了。在这种情况下，让我们来看看会发生什么。我们要把F加回去
into the graph. And. And look at all, and look at it's neighbors and we see that we
添加到图表中。和。看看所有的，看看它的邻居，我们看到我们
have a neighbor that's using r1. We have a neighbor that's using r2 and we have a
有一个邻居正在使用R1。我们有一个邻居正在使用R2，我们有一个
neighbor that's using r2 and we have a neighbor that's using r3. And so on in
邻居使用R2，我们有一个邻居使用R3。以此类推
this case, optimistic coloring will not work so in fact F had more than K
在这种情况下，乐观着色不会起作用，所以实际上F超过了K
neighbors and after we color the sub-graph, it turns out that those
邻居，在我们给子图上色之后，结果发现那些
neighbors are using all K. In this case three, all three of the register names.
邻居使用的都是K，在本例中是三个，全部三个寄存器名称。
And so F where there is no register left over for F and we're going to have to
也就是说，没有剩余的寄存器了，我们将不得不
actually spill it and store in memory. So, if optimistic coloring fails as it does in
实际上是把它洒出来并储存在内存中。因此，如果乐观着色失败，就像在
this example, then we spill f. So, what we're going to do is allocate the memory
在这个例子中，我们会泄漏f。所以，我们要做的是分配内存
location for f and typically, what that means is that we'll allocate a position in
f的位置，通常，这意味着我们将在
the current stack frame. Let's call this address fa for the address of f. And then
当前堆栈帧。让我们称这个地址为f的地址，然后
we're going to modify the control flow graph. We're going to change the code for
我们将修改控制流图。我们要将代码更改为
that compiling. So, before each operation that reads f, we're going to insert a load
那个汇编。因此，在每个读取f的操作之前，我们将插入一个加载
that loads from that address to current value of f into a temporary name. Okay,
其从该地址到当前值f加载到临时名称中。好吧,
that makes sense because if the value is out of memory, then if we have an
这是有意义的，因为如果值内存不足，那么如果我们有一个
operation that needs to actually use the value. We're going to have to load it from
操作，该操作需要实际使用该值。我们要把它从
a memory first then to the register. And similarly after each operation that writes
首先是存储器，然后是寄存器。类似地，在写入的每个操作之后
F, we're going to insert the store so we're going to save the current value of F
，我们要插入存储，所以我们要保存F的当前值
into it's location in memory. So, here is the original code from which we
它在内存中的位置。所以，这是我们从中提取的原始代码
constructed the registry interference graph and notice that there are few
构建了注册表干扰图，并注意到
references to f in here and we just highlight them, alright. So, we have a
在这里引用f，我们只突出显示它们，好的。所以，我们有一个
couple of reads, we have a right and so now, what are we going to do? So, here
读了几遍，我们就有了权利，那么现在我们要做什么呢？所以，在这里
we had the use of F, the read of F in this statement and now we preceded that by
我们在这条语句中使用了F，也就是F的读法，现在我们在前面加上
a load. And notice that I've given a new name here. I've called this F1. And, that's
一大笔钱。请注意，我在这里给了一个新名称。我把这叫做F1。还有，那就是
because the different uses of F in the control flow graph don't all have to have
因为F在控制流图中的不同用法并不都必须具有
the same temporary name. And actually it would be a good idea to separate them so
相同的临时名称。实际上，把它们分开会是个好主意
each distinct to use of F will get it's own name. So here we load the value of F
使用F的每个DISTINCT都会有自己的名称。所以我们在这里加载F的值
and then it get to use in the statement. Here we have a right to f and so we store
然后在语句中使用它。在这里，我们有权使用f，所以我们存储
the current value of f and those argument to a different name, f2. So, that's
f的当前值和其他名称f2的参数。所以，这就是
temporary is computed here as going to be stored and it's called f2. And finally,
临时值在这里被计算为将被存储，它被称为f2。最后，
the third use of f there's another load of f right here. Which is then used in this
f的第三个用法，这里还有一个f。然后将其用于此
computation here of b. Okay. So, that is the systematic way to modify the code to
这里计算b，好的。因此，这是将代码修改为
use f in storage. And now, we have to recompute the aliveness of f. And so, what
在存储中使用f。现在，我们必须重新计算f的活性，那么，
happens there. Well, here is the original aliveness information from which we
发生在那里。好的，这是原始的活体信息，我们从这些信息中
computed the register interference graph, okay. And now notice that f is gone. We no
计算了寄存器干扰图，好的。现在请注意，f已经消失了。我们没有
longer use f in the programs so we can delete all the places where we mentioned
在程序中不再使用f，这样我们就可以删除我们提到的所有位置
that f was live and now we have the three new names, f1, f2, and f3. And we have to
那个f是实况转播的，现在我们有了三个新名字，f1，f2和f3。我们必须要
add in their aliveness information so it creates a new program points here where we
添加他们的活跃度信息，以便在此处创建一个新的计划点，我们
inserted statements. And of course, where we have a load of the current value of f
插入的语句。当然，我们有一大堆f的当前值
that value if live right before the use in the next statement. Here, we have the
该值如果正好在下一条语句中使用之前有效。在这里，我们有
right of the current value of f and that's live right before the store and then
在f的当前值的右边，它就在商店前面，然后
here's another load of the current value of f which is live until the store, I'm
这是另一个加载的f的当前值，它一直持续到商店，我是
sorry, until the use in the next statement. Okay. And so, now notice here
抱歉，在下一条语句中使用之前。好吧。所以，现在请注意这里
that f used to be live in many, many, many places in the, in the code. And now not
在代码中，f曾经住在很多很多地方。现在不是了
only is f or the, the different versions of f live in fewer places also we've
只是f或者，f的不同版本生活在更少的地方，我们也有
distinguish them. So, it actually separate the different uses of f and so this will
把它们区分开来。因此，它实际上将f的不同用法分开，所以这将
have their own nodes in their own set of interferences in the graph and they won't
在图中的自己的干涉集中有自己的结点，并且它们不会
share them with the other users of f and that will actually also reduce the number
与f的其他用户共享它们，这实际上也会减少
of edges in the graph. To summarize the example on the previous slide, once we
图形中的边数。总结上一张幻灯片上的示例，一旦我们
have decided that we are actually going to spill a temporary f, that means we're
已经决定我们实际上要泄漏一个临时的f，这意味着我们
going to change the program where have loads and stores to the program and now
正在将程序的加载和存储位置更改为程序，现在
we're going to have a different program and that's going to change our register
我们将有一个不同的程序，这将改变我们的注册表
allocation problems. We're going to have to recompute the aliveness of information,
分配问题。我们将不得不重新计算信息的活性，
we're have to rebuild the restrain interference graph and then we're going to
我们必须重建约束干涉图，然后我们要
have to try again to color that block graph. Now, it turns out that this new
我得再试一次给挡路图表上色。现在，事实证明，这个新的
aliveness information is almost the same as it was before. So, all the temporary
活跃度信息几乎和以前一样。所以，所有临时性的
names other than f are not much affected by the by the new statements that are
f以外的名称不会受到影响较大的新语句的影响，这些新语句是
added. There are a few program points where they might be live but I replaced
添加了。有几个程序点可能是现场直播的，但我替换了
they were alive before and they're still alive. And, F itself has changed fairly
他们以前还活着，现在还活着。而且，F本身也发生了相当大的变化
dramatically. It's like this information has changed really dramatically. Certainly
戏剧性的。这个信息好像真的发生了戏剧性的变化。当然
the old name F is no longer used and so it's like this information goes away and
旧名字F不再使用，所以这个信息好像消失了，
then we've also split F into three in this case three different temporaries. One for
然后我们也把F分成三部分，在这种情况下是三个不同的时间段。一张是
each of the different uses of F in the control flow graph. And I noticed that
F在控制流图中的不同用法。我注意到
each of these new uses of F or these new versions of F is live in a very, very
F的每一种新用法或F的这些新版本都生活在一个非常、非常
small area so a load. In this video, we are going to continue our discussion of
面积很小，所以负荷很大。在这段视频中，我们将继续讨论
as filling. For a load instruction The thing that were loading the temporary that
作为填充物。对于加载指令，加载临时
we're loading fi is live only between the load and the next instruction where it's
我们正在加载的FI只在加载和下一条指令之间有效，在下一条指令中
used and similarly for a store. It's score of a temporary fi is live only between the
用于商店，类似地用于商店。它的分数是临时的FI只在
store itself and the proceeding instruction. The one they created fi. And
存储自身和后续指令。就是他们创造的那个菲。和
the effective is, is to greatly reduce the live range of the spilled variable. So,
有效的是，大大缩小了溢出变量的生存范围。所以,
whatever name we decide to spill by adding the load and stores right next to the
无论我们决定通过将加载和存储添加到
places where those values are used We dramatically reduced the live range and in
使用这些值的地方我们极大地缩小了活动范围
addition, as I mentioned in the previous live by splitting the name f into multiple
另外，正如我在上一次直播中提到的，通过将名称f分成多个
different name, we also you know, avoid sharing. Those different liv e ranges
不同的名字，我们也是你知道的，避免分享。那些不同的生活范围
between the different versions of F. So because the live range of F is reduced by
不同版本的F之间的差异。因此，因为F的有效范围减少了
spilling. It has fewer interferences in the new program than it did in the old
打翻了。它对新程序的干扰比对旧程序的干扰要少
program. And so what that means the particulars in the rebuild [inaudible]
程序。那么，重建过程中的细节[听不见]意味着什么呢？
interference graph, F will have fewer neighbors. Some of the neighbors that it
干涉图，F将具有较少的邻居。一些邻居认为它
had before have gone away because it just live in fewer places. So if we look at the
已经消失了，因为它们只是生活在更少的地方。所以如果我们看一下
new register interference graph, we can see that among all the different versions
新的寄存器干扰图，我们可以看到在所有不同的版本中
of F. Remember that F has been split into three temporaries in this graph. We see
记住F在这个图中被分成了三个时间段。我们看到了
that they only interfere with D and C. Whereas, before f have several other
它们只干扰D和C，而在f有其他几个
neighbors in the graph. And now, in fact this new graph is three tolerable. Of
图中的邻居。现在，实际上这个新的图是三个可以容忍的。的
course it might be the case that we can't just spill one name. We might have to have
当然，情况可能是这样，我们不能只说出一个名字。我们可能不得不
just spill several different temporaries before the coloring is found. And, the
在找到着色剂之前，只需洒出几个不同的临时颜色即可。而且，这个
tricky part is to siding what to spill. So, this is the hard decision that has to
棘手的部分是把要洒的东西放在一边。所以，这是一个艰难的决定
be made during restore allocation. Now any choice is correct. It's only a question of
在还原分配期间执行。现在任何选择都是正确的。这只是一个问题
performance so you know some choices of spilling will lead to better code than
性能，因此您知道一些溢出选项将产生比以下选项更好的代码
others but any choice of spilling is going to resolve in a correct program. And
除了任何泄漏的选择之外，其他的都将在一个正确的程序中解决。和
there's heuristics that people use to pick which temporaries to spill and here are a
有一些试探法，人们用来选择要泄漏的临时文件，这里是一个
few or I think three of the most popular ones. One is to spill the temporaries and
我认为最受欢迎的有三个，少之又少。一种是把临时文件和
have the most conflicts. And the reason for that is that this is the temporary.
有最多的冲突。原因是这是暂时的。
The one thing that you can move into memory that will most affect the number of
您可以移动到内存中的一件事将最大程度地影响
interferences in the graph. So, the idea is by possible spilling justice on
图形中的干涉。所以，这个想法是通过可能的伸张正义
variable. We'll remove enough edges from the graph that they becomes tolerable with
变量。我们将从图中删除足够多的边，使它们变得可以容忍
the number of registers we have. Another possibility is a spilled temporaries that
我们拥有的登记簿的数量。另一种可能性是泄漏的临时文件
have few definitions and uses. And, here the idea is that by spilling those since
几乎没有定义和用途。而且，这里的想法是，通过泄漏这些，因为
they're not used very much, the number of lows in storage will have to add, will be
它们的使用率不是很高，存储低点的数量将不得不增加，将是
relatively small and so if a variable just isn't used in many places, then the actual
相对较小，因此如果变量在很多地方没有使用，那么实际的
cost, in terms of additional instructions that are going to be executed to spill it,
成本，就将要执行以溢出它的额外指令而言，
is relatively small. And another one and this is actually the one that I think that
相对较小。还有另一个，实际上这就是我认为
all the compilers implement is to avoid spilling an inner loops. So, if you have a
所有编译器的实现都是为了避免溢出内部循环。所以，如果你有一个
choice between spilling a variable that's used within the. Innermost loop for the
控件中使用的变量溢出之间的选择。对象的最里面的循环
program and one that is used some place else. You probably preferred this that you
程序和在其他地方使用的程序。你可能更喜欢这样，因为你
spill the one that is used not in the innermost loop absolutely because again,
绝对泄漏不在最里面循环中使用的那个，因为再说一遍，
that will result in fewer loads in stores. You really want to avoid adding additional
这将导致商店中的装载量减少。是否确实要避免添加其他
instructions to your inner loop.
指示您的内循环。